Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Additional Correspondence
    - Correspondence: Jusuf Wanandi, Winston Lord and Holbrooke, 1984-89 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Lakeside School (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Yap Thiam Hien (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - LIPI Conference, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - University of Leiden, 1993-94 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Tom Rankin Correspondence, 1992-98 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - David Ransom: Ramparts, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Susan Rogers Correspondence, 1978-92 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Elizabeth (Basil) Rauch Correspondence, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Mavis Rose Correspondence, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Geoffrey Robinson Correspondence I, 1967-96 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Geoffrey Robinson Correspondence II, 1991-93 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Geoffrey Robinson Correspondence III, 1978-93 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Caleb Rossiter Correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Jack & Wanda Ryan Correspondence, 1995-98 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Jonathon Schell Correspondence, 1989-93 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - M.B. Schnapper Correspondence, 1965-88 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Jan Scholte Correspondence, 1986-95 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Mark Seldon Correspondence, 1983-96 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Allain Seznec Correspondence, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Harold Shadick: Memorial, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Stephen SHalom Correspondence, 1987-88 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Hassan Shadily Correspondence, 1952-91 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Toni Shapiro Correspondence, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Sayuri Shimizu Correspondence, 1986-92 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Masaya + Aiko Shiraishi Correspondence, 1973-93 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Sandra Siegel Correspondence, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Selo Soemardjan Correspondence, 1980-94 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Nim Chee Siew Correspondence I, 1991-94 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Nim Chee Siew Correspondence II, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Nim Chee Siew Correspondence III, 1992-98 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Josef & Lynn Silverstein Correspondence, 1978-96 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Harapan Sinar Correspondence, 1987-95 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Poppy Sjahrir Correspondence, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Nodari Simonia Correspondence, 1979-88 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Nana, Koko, & Soedjatmoko Correspondence, 1957-92 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Soedjatmokos & Sudarpos Correspondence, 1962-95 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Soebadio Article, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Blema Steinberg Correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - SOAS Correspondence, 1991-93 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - SOAS Data, 1991-92 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Arthur Sulzberger Correspondence, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Laura Summers Correspondence, 1984-98 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Ann Swift Correspondence, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Taube Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Abdullah Taufik Correspondence, 1990-95 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Bob Taylor Correspondence, 1978-92 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Nora Taylor Correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Nora Taylor/Stan Correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Telephone Correspondence, 1991-92 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Nguyen Thi Thanh Correspondence, 1978-93 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Thanh Correspondence, 1988-92 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - General Thi Correspondence, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 48)
    - Kamala Tiyavanich Correspondence, 1989-96 (Box 41, Folder 49)
    - Rahman Tolleng Correspondence, 1996-97 (Box 41, Folder 50)
    - Robert Topmiller Correspondence, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 51)
    - Toyota Foundation Correspondence, 1987-93 (Box 41, Folder 52)
    - Jim Trullinger Correspondence I, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 53)
    - Jim Trullinger Correspondence II, 1980-96 (Box 41, Folder 54)
    - Steve Tukel Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 41, Folder 55)
    - Takashi Uehara Correspondence, 1989-94 (Box 41, Folder 56)
    - Francis Underhill Correspondence, 1980-93 (Box 41, Folder 57)
    - Esta Unger Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 41, Folder 58)
    - Thaveenporn Vasavakul Correspondence I, 1993-97 (Box 41, Folder 59)
    - Thaveenporn Vasavakul Correspondence II, 1963-93 (Box 41, Folder 60)
    - Paul W. van der Veur Correspondence, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 61)
    - Eliza Van Hollen Correspondence, 1980-98 (Box 41, Folder 62)
    - Bob & Elaise Van Niel Correspondence, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 63)
    - Vollerman Correspondence, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 64)
    - Chieu Ngu Vu Correspondence, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 65)
    - Sandy Walker Correspondence, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 66)
    - Sheryl Walter Correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 41, Folder 67)
    - Leslie Watson Correspondence, 1980-95 (Box 41, Folder 68)
    - Donald Weatherbee Correspondence, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 69)
    - Jayne Werner Correspondence I, 1978-93 (Box 41, Folder 70)
    - Jayne Werner Correspondence II, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 71)
    - Linda & Frank Weinstein Correspondence, 1990-97 (Box 41, Folder 72)
    - Webb Correspondence, 1984-87 (Box 41, Folder 73)
    - Ingrid Wessel Correspondence, 1993-98 (Box 41, Folder 74)
    - Chris White Correspondence, 1981-96 (Box 41, Folder 75)
    - C. Wiebes Correspondence, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 76)
    - John Wilkinson Correspondence, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 77)
    - Dave Williams Correspondence, 1989-95 (Box 41, Folder 78)
    - Marilyn Williams Correspondence, 1986-96 (Box 41, Folder 79)
    - Mike Williams Correspondence, 1990-93 (Box 41, Folder 80)
    - Don & Liz Willmot Correspondence, 1987-96 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - David & Kathy Wurfel Correspondence, 1988-95 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Jeffrey Winters Correspondence, 1996-98 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Yale U. Press Correspondence, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Linda Yarr Correspondence, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Linda York Correspondence, 1987-91 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Marilyn Young Correspondence, 1982-91 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Mestika Zed Correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Robert Zelnich Correspondence, 1967-93 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Stephen Zunes Correspondence, 1987-95 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Masako Yamanouchi, 1967-68 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Anuncha Chansuriya Correspondence, 1986-88 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Rattikul Chansuriya Correspondence I, 1986-93 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Rattikul Chansuriya Correspondence II, 1988-93 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Efren Saz Correspondence, 1987-93 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - A Correspondence, 1978-95 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Samuel Berger Correspondence, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - B Correspondence I, 1978-96 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - B Correspondence II, 1980-95 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - C Correspondence, 1978-98 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - D-E Correspondence, 1978-93 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - F-G Correspondence, 1978-96 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - H Correspondence, 1978-93 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Tom Harrison Correspondence, 1958-69 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - I-J Correspondence, 1976-98 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - K Correspondence, 1978-96 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - L Correspondence, 1978-96 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - M Correspondence, 1978-99 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - N-O Correspondence, 1972-95 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - P-Q Correspondence, 1979-98 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Q-R Correspondence, 1970-96 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Correspondence
    - Ben Abel Correspondence, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Benedict Anderson Correspondence I, 1966-97 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Ben Anderson-AAAS Correspondence I, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Replacement of SEA Faculty, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Ben Anderson-AAAS Correspondence II, 1983-94 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Ben Anderson-SEAP Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Benedict Anderson Correspondence II, 1981-94 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Ben Anderson-Frederick-Brian Kie Correspondence, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Lim Bian-Kie Correspondence, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Govt. 344, 1970-73 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Ben Anderson-Singapore Correspondence, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Ben Anderson-Phillipines Correspondence, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Ben Anderson-Binenkorb Correspondence, 1987-88 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Ben Anderson Correspondence III, 1988-95 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Ben Anderson Feb 7-14 Correspondence, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Ben Anderson-writings etc., 1980 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Indonesian Studies Group, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - John Badgley Correspondence, 1986-95 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - SEAP: Bagley Feb-March Correspondence, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Bagley-Lindseth Southeast Asia Trip Report, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Milton Barnette: Obituary & Scholarship Endowment, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Randy Barker Correspondence, 1991-94 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Abby Cohn: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Walter Coward Correspondence, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Gerard Diffloth Correspondence, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Gary Fields: Econ, 1982-84 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Paul Gellert Correspondence, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Clara Golay Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Frank Golay Correspondence, 1976-92 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Golay M.S., n.d. (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Paul Gellert Correspondence, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Martin Hotch Correspondence, 1980-98 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Deborah Homsher Correspondence, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Franklin Huffman Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Huynh Khanh: Memorial Service, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Huynh Khanh: Memorial, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Khanh-Obituary & Biography, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Khanh Correspondence, 1982-90 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Tom Kirsch Correspondence, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Kaja McGowan Correspondence, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Stan O'Connor Correspondence I, 1979-98 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Stan O'Connor Correspondence II, 1987-95 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Giok Po Oey Correspondence, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - Allen Riedy Correspondence, 1994-97 (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - Jim Siegel Correspondence, 1984-91 (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Lauriston Sharp Interview, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - Lauriston Sharp Prize, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - Sharp-G.K File, 1978-94 (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Saya Shiraishi Correspondence I, 1991-95 (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Saya Shiraishi Correspondence II, 1987-93 (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Saya Shiraishi Correpsondence III, 1993-99 (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Takashi Shiraishi Correspondence, 1988-96 (Box 43, Folder 52)
    - Nancy Stage Correspondence, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - Larry Stifel Correspondence, 1983-95 (Box 43, Folder 54)
    - Helen Swank Correspondence I, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 55)
    - Helen Swank Correspondence II, 1973-94 (Box 43, Folder 56)
    - Keith Taylor Correspondence, 1987-95 (Box 43, Folder 57)
    - Keith Taylor-640 Fall Correspondence, 1994-95 (Box 43, Folder 58)
    - Keith Taylor-Vietnamese Culuture Studies, 1987-95 (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - Erik Thorebecke Correspondence, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Whoatly Thah Correspondence, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 61)
    - Dave Wyatt Correspondence, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 62)
    - Government Appointment of Successor, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 63)
    - Government Dept. Faculty, 1990-94 (Box 43, Folder 64)
    - Randolph Barker Correspondence, 1988-90 (Box 43, Folder 65)
    - Herbert Briggs Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 66)
    - Martin Bernal Correspondence, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 67)
    - Susan Buck-Morss Correspondence, 1982-83 (Box 43, Folder 68)
    - Werner Dannhauser Correspondence, 1980-92 (Box 43, Folder 69)
    - Arch Dotson Correpsondence, 1969-73 (Box 43, Folder 70)
    - Milton Esman Correspondence, 1971-87 (Box 43, Folder 71)
    - Davydd Greenwood & Michael Goldfield Correspondence, 1985-87 (Box 43, Folder 72)
    - Benjamin Ginsberg Correspondence, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 73)
    - James Goldeier: USSR Article, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 74)
    - Steve Jackson Correspondence I, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 75)
    - Steve Jackson Correspondence II, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 76)
    - Kahin Prize-I.R., 1990 (Box 43, Folder 77)
    - Bud Kenworthy Correspondence, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 78)
    - Mary Kotzenstein Correspondence, 1986-88 (Box 43, Folder 79)
    - Ronald King Correspondence, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 80)
    - Peter Katzenstein Correspondence, 1976-89 (Box 43, Folder 81)
    - Isaac Kramnick Correspondence, 1983-88 (Box 43, Folder 82)
    - Isaac Kramnick: Materials on Right Wing, 1981-84 (Box 43, Folder 83)
    - Isaac Kramnick Correspondence-May 1979, 1979-86 (Box 43, Folder 84)
    - Richard Ned Lebow Correspondence, 1982-90 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Ariel Levite Correpondence (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Theodore Lowi Correspondence, 1987-88 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Patricia Leeds Correspondence, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Pontusson Correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - T.J. Pempell Correspondence, 1981-87 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Pigeons/McGraw Correspondence, 1986-87 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - George Quester Correspondence, 1973-82 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Jeremy Rabkin-Mary Katzenstein Correspondence, 1983-88 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Jeremy Rabkin Correspondence, 1982-87 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Dick Rosecrance Correspondence, 1979-87 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Rhodes Correspondence, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Judith Reppy Correspondence, 1983-87 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Martin Shefter Correspondence, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Myron Rush Correspondence, 1987-93 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Lauriston Sharp Correspondence, 1970-93 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Lawrence Schienman Correspondence, 1984-86 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Marty Shifter Correspondence, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Sidney Tarrow Correspondence, 1980-92 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Norman Uphoff Correspondence, 1976-87 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Norman Uphoff Correspondence, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Vivienne Shue Correspondence, 1983-92 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Government Search Committee: I.R. & C.G., 1982-83 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - S-Correspondence I, 1983-96 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - S-Correspondence II, 1978-93 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - T-Correspondence, 1978-96 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - U-V Correspondence, 1981-96 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - W-Z Correspondence I, 1978-96 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - W-Z Correspondence II, 1978-94 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Series IV. Teaching, Research Materials and Lectures
  - Japan occupation; U.S. establishment of separate state (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - AS 601/Government 652 materials, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - AS 601/Government 300 materials, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Jim Coyle & Esta Unger correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Government 300.2 class, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Maps (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Maps continued (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper articles and random materials, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Course materials for Government 687 as well as other miscellaneous materials, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Exams & Alan Epstein materials, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Government 387 materials, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Classroom handouts, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - The Marshall Mission and its Aftermath (a lecture) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Yalta materials (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Manchuria lecture, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - China and the rise of Mao lecture; as well as maps (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - American-Korean relations in the 19th century, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Moscow, the KMT and the Chinese Communists: 1920-24 (a lecture) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Imperialism and Social Darwinism (a lecture) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - China through 1860 U.S.; relations & the opening of Japan (lectures) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Government 300; Vietnam war, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Government 300 random materials, 1982-84 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Government 300.2 random materials, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Information from Duke University (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Gov"t 315-reading lists, 1952-61 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Government 314 exams, 1953-61 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Government 314 class lists and essays, 1952-62 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Government 377 lectures, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Various Vietnam lectures (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Government 387, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Government 387, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - China-Introduction (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Government 314- notes (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Government 314-China 1, Sept. 28, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Government 314-China 2, Sept. 30, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Government 314-China 3, Oct. 1, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Government 314-China 4-7, Oct. 5-Feb. 27, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Government 314-China 8-12, 1955-61 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Government 314-China 13-14, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Materials on Vietnam, 1966-67 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Course materials for 601 & 102, 1957-58 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Course materials for 602, 1953-57 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Government 377 materials, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Government 314; Kashmir, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Government 314; Pakistan (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Government 314-India, 1954-60 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Government 314; Japan-1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Government 314; Japan 2-3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Government 314; Japan 4-6 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Government 314; Japan 7-9 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Government 314; Japan 10 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Course 644, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Government 377-The U.S. & Asia, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Government 377-random materials, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Government 387-The United States and Asia, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Government 387-random materials, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Government 300-Indochina, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Course materials, 1950-52 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Government 395-Seminar: Political Problem of Asia, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Asian Studies 501, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - AS 501-Seminar on SEA (Indonesia), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - FES 975-Art & Soc in Modern Indonesia, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Government 331-Indochina, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Government 577-Seminar in Intl. Relations of SEA, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Government 344-random materials (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Government 387-random materials, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Social Darwinism & Annex of Philippines (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Course 502-reports (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - FES 601, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - FES 601-Pre-Colonial European Contact with SEA, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - FES 601, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - FES 601-reading lists, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Course 387 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - FES 601-Indonesia, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - FES 602-random materials, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Government 502-Asian Studies, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Government 300.2-random materials, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - AS 502 Indonesia Seminar-readings (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Government 342, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Indonesia I, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - FES 601-Exams, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Thailand & Dominos, May 8, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Indochina, Apr. 28, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Laos, Apr. 10, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Japan and the U.S., Dec. 1, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Materials on Korea (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Indochina III-V (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Indochina III-V (continued) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - U.S. and China, Apr. 24, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - China Discussion, Mar. 7, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - China Discussion, Apr. 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Philippines, Apr. 23, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Philippines II (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Government 315-China 15 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Government 315-China 16 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Korea Materials (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Korea Materials (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Korea Materials, May 6, 1986 & May 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Philippines Materials, May 8, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Philippines Materials, Mar. 10, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Philippines Materials (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Open Door Notes, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Indonesia and the U.S., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - U.S. and Post War China (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - U.S. and China (1941-44) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Washington Conference; Immigration and Racial discrimination (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Materials on China (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Issue of Recognition of Red China (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - China materials (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Russo-Japanese Rapprochement under Stalin (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1937-40 Japan and the U.S. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - June 1940-41 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Korea materials (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Korea materials (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Korea materials, Mar. 14, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Post-war Japan (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam-discussions, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Korea and American Foreign Policy (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Japan materials (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Japan materials (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Vietnam I-V, 1980-83 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam VI (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Government 387, 1962-74 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Government 387, 1979-80 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Government 387-Readings and Changes, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Government 387, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Government 687, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - 300.1 The Vietnam War-readings (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Government 387, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Government 652 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Government 687, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Examples of good exams (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - 300.1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Class materials (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - 300.1-example essays (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - 300.1-Gareth Porter negotiations (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Government 687, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Government 652, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Government 687, 1978-81 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Government 387 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Government 300, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Government 387, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Government 387, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Government 387, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Government 387, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Government 387, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Government 300, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Government 300, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Government 687, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Government 331, Sept. 25, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Government 331, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Government 652-Political Problems of S.E.A., 1974 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Japan materials, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Government of India 2-4 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Keysort card categories (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Government 331-Indochina (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Government 331-readings (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Government 377 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Government 377, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Government 577, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - FES 201, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - FES 202, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - FES 202, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - FES 202-reading lists (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - FES 202, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - FES 202-Malaya (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - FES 202-Malaya-I (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - FES 202-Malaya-II (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - FES 952-Chinese in Southeast Asia (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - FES 951-Communism (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - FES 951-Comintern (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - FES 952 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - East Asia Advisory Panel, Apr. 27, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam-teach-in (Washington)-general correspondence (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Random materials (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Vietnam materials (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - History 885 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Air Force Lecture (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Air Force Talk, July 1962 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - FES 975-Communications Seminar, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 25)